Dress Up Camera
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi.me/OrangeFlash
Oh no!
Ouch...
Mud is all over my clothes!
But I don't care!
Nobita-kun, getting soaked by rain is not good for your body!
I'm home!
Daddy, look at this!
Later.
Please... look at it!
I'm busy now! Later.
Just a moment... Please look! Daddy! Don't you like this lovely coat?
Yeah, it is! But I have no money now. Let's buy it next time.
Nobita, your shirt is dirty once again!
You wore it on just moments ago!
Please be considerate about your mother as well, from next time!.
Weather inside the home is bad as well.
Change in to these!
If you dirty your shirt again, you'll have no dress to wear!
You're dirty from head to toe! Go and take a bath!
Okay, I'll take a bath.
This is all daddy's fault, If only he had bought that coat for her...
Did you do something once again, Nobita?
Nothing really!
Oh, no, she scolded me just now and this happens...
You need a shirt to wear, right?
Yeah!
Dress Up Camera!
How to use that?
What kind of shirt would you like to wear, Nobita-kun?
let me think...
How about a superman-like styled shirt?
I wanted to wear a space suit too.
Oh, your thoughts are so vivid as usual!
Maybe I went a little too over-board!
I'll draw the shirt now!
Would you prefer this shirt?
It looks cool!
Project the drawing in to camera and aim the shutter on you.
Perfectly align the shirt on your body!
Then press the shutter!
So great!
How did you do that?
Piece of cake! The theory is very simple!
You can do it only if you think of the game of lining bricks.
We can combine and metamorphose the bricks into different shapes, right?
This uses the same logic as that.
We combined scattered dress numerators into the camera.
I can create any shirt I like?
Yeah, any design is okay!
Lend it to me for a moment!
What are you drawing?
A costume for Doraemon.
Why did you draw me Circus Joker Monkey's dress?
It looks good on you!
That's it! I'll gift Mum her favorite dress.
Is this the magazine that has Mum's favorite coat?
This one!
What?
Dear, how could you?
You got this coat even when my pocket was empty?
Huh?
A present for you, Mum!
I'm going to show off this camera.
Don't get carried away!
Black cat, don't you wish your skin and hair color was different?
just you wait!
I'll make you beautiful so that all other cats will envy you!
It's Teacher!
I'll present you a handsome dress!
He will look young, tall and handsome wearing this!
Oops!
I made a mistake!
Is that so?
I'll give you two fitting dress!
More lovely ones!
What are you wearing?
How girly!
You look funny!
Why are you wearing a girl's skirt?
You look like a fool!
This is too embarrassing!
Oh, is this Nobita's doing?
You did it, right?
Oh, no!
Wait, Nobita!
Don't run away, Nobita!
You dare change our dresses to that of girls'?
Wait and see! We'll teach you a good lesson!
Please forgive me.
I won't do that next time!
Please forgive me!
A girl shouldn't do rough stuff!
What? I'm not a girl!
I'd better run away!
What? Suneo took away my camera?
Sorry.
How hopeless are you!
Suneo is so full of himself!
This camera will help me fulfill my dream!
Your dream?
I feel shy and don't know what to say.
Look!
What's this?
Models!
I want to be a fashion designer, so I'm studying it.
Really?
I have also secretly....
my real dream is to be a fashion model.
A fashion model?
I'll take advantage of my strapping body of man!
That's wonderful!
I know, right? Let's host a fashion show!
Good idea!
Now we'll host a fashion show, a like of which, no one has ever seen before!
Ladies, you all need to choose your dresses one after another, while on the stage.
Great...
Are you ready?
OK!
I've already placed various designs in the camera.
So let's begin!
How embrasasing!
It's not my fault!
Stop it, you jerk!
Giant became naked. But how did you do that?
I switched the designs with a blank white paper.